tafford.com 2012-05-10

# Privacy Policy

### Tafford Privacy Policy

Information Collection and Use At Tafford, we are committed to taking appropriate measures to ensure that all information you provide us is handled in accordance with this policy. The information you provide to us is used to process your order, service your account, facilitate your transactions with our third party marketing partners, and to improve our site's content and functionality and enhance your experience as a consumer, as further described below.

### Order Information

We request information from you as part of the order process, which requires you to provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). All this information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer orders. If we have trouble processing an order, your contact information is used to get in touch with you.

### Personal Information

The information you provide is used to process and bill your orders and contact you when any problems are encountered. We may also send you information about our company's new services and special offers unless you elect not to receive such offers. From time to time, we make our mailing list (names and mailing addresses only) and general shopping activity available to carefully screened companies whose products we believe will be of interest to you and whose privacy practices meet the Direct Marketing Association's privacy standards. We do not share email addresses for this purpose.

In some cases, we permit third parties to offer their goods and services to our customers, and will share your information, including credit/debit card numbers and other billing information with such third parties in order to facilitate your transactions with them.

If you prefer that we do not share any of your information with these companies, please contact us to "opt-out" and we will not share your information for this purpose. Please understand that if you opt-out, and later accept an offer from an advertiser or one of our third party marketing partners, we will share your information with that specific third party.

### How We Use Email

When you provide us your email address, we may send you emails necessary to process your order, respond to a request, provide customer service, or promote products or services. For example, after you place an order at tafford.com, you will receive an email confirmation and, in most cases, an email with package tracking information. It is our intent to send promotional emails only to those persons who wish to receive them. We provide instructions on how to unsubscribe in each promotional email and within the "Contact Us" section of the Privacy Policy on the Tafford web site.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data stored on a user's computer in the form of a text file. We use cookies in our system to provide a full featured user experience as well as to aid in other tracking capabilities. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, our site will use an encrypted cookie that will allow the user to establish a logged in session. Once their session is established they will not need to re-log in there-after while browsing the site. The user's login credentials, such as their password, are not stored and are not vulnerable to compromise. We take all precautions to secure all account information. A user has complete control over a site's ability to create and store cookies. If, through browser settings or internet security software, the user disables the use of all types of cookies, the user may not be able to successfully complete an order on our web site.

We also use pixel tags - tiny graphic images - to tell us what parts of our Web site you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us. We may also contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie in our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies.

### Data Sharing

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. When a customer enters an order on our website, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to proceed the services mentioned above. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or a legal process served on our website. We may also share information as explained above under the "Personal Information" section.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tafford is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When you place an order with us, you are using our secure e-commerce server and secure server software (SSL). This means that all of the information you enter is encrypted before we receive it. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just "surfing". While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about the security at our website, wish to opt-out as described above under the "Personal Information" Section, or if you prefer not to receive catalogs or other communications from Tafford, please contact us at:  
Tafford Uniforms  
Attn: Customer Service  
104 Park Drive  
Montgomeryville, PA 18936

CustomerService@tafford.com

Please note that if you opt-out after we have provided your contact information to third parties for the purposes described above in "Personal Information," such opt-out will only apply to our handling and disclosure of your information and will not apply to those third parties to whom your information has already been provided. If you wish to no longer receive offers from such third parties, we suggest that you contact them directly. Moreover, as indicated in the Personal Information section, if you opt-out and later accept an offer from an advertiser or one of our third party marketing partners, we will share your information with that specific third party. Please be sure to provide us your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog, so that we can be sure to identify you correctly. Because mailings are planned in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If, due to human error, you continue to receive unwanted communications, please contact us again and we will make every effort to correct the situation as soon as possible.

### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your address), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by clicking the "Your Account" link on any page on the website and making the desired changes, or by visiting our Customer Service Center.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and the circumstances, if any, under which we disclose it. It is important to remember that by using our site or making any purchases from us, you agree t the terms of this privacy policy, including any changes that we may make from time to time.

### Transfer of Information

In the event our company is ever sold, we reserve the right to transfer ownership of our customer information to the acquiring company.
